Hello, Dad?
Did you get what I sent?
Yes, child, the logo
and the address.
Many operations have failed
because of them and their
companions.
It's a spy camera.
There's someone I need to catch.
Sir, I have a feeling
that Berdugo's laboratory
is here.
Aren't we going to talk about
what happened to us
in the North?
Do you really think
I'll believe you didn't know
I'd be excluded?
Joey...
Sir Andrew.
I'll be the one
to take Joey home.
I don't want you to.
Come on.
Tell your family
who you really are.
You are Berdugo!
This should help you relax.
[GROANS]
What did you do, Ma'am Rebecca?
Ma'am Rebecca!
Quick, call an ambulance!
Ma'am Yvette! Come quickly!
It's Ma'am Rebecca!
- Ma'am!
- It's mommy!
- Mommy!
- Ma'am! Ma'am!
Mom, wake up!
- Mom! Wake up, Mommy!
- Ma'am, Ma'am!
Tomas, where are you?
Let's take mommy
to the hospital.
You cannot live, Rebecca.
They cannot know the truth.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
We don't have those parts.
There's no order yet.
You better come back tomorrow.
- Okay, tomorrow?
- Yes, tomorrow, come back.
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[REVVING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey.
You were inside the room
when the transaction
in the North happened, right?
Did you see Berdugo?
Were you be able
to identify him?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you permit, Berdugo.
[SHATTERS]
Oh my gosh.
No.
You, do you know who Berdugo is?
[GUN FIRING]
Castro, let's go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
I didn't see his face.
Joey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for this late apology.
I kept justifying my decisions
instead of apologizing.
And I know I hurt you.
Many times, actually.
For not telling you that...
Zoey was my ex.
Or my negligence that kept you
out of operations.
And lastly,
for breaking my promise
to find Berdugo.
[PHONE RINGING]
Dad?
Joey, my child.
Your Korean friend,
do you still talk to him?
Who? Jin Ho?
Not yet. Why?
Because you mentioned that
he suddenly disappeared, right?
That he stopped contacting you?
Maybe he already caught
the syndicate member
he was looking for.
The one you said
who killed Ramon?
Yes.
Maybe he returned to Korea,
that's why he's gone.
- Why are you asking?
- Nothing.
I'm just thinking of another way
to track Berdugo.
Maybe he really left.
All right, dear, thank you.
Okay, Dad.
Love you.
Major Delgado is asking
about Jin Ho?
Yes.
He probably thinks Jin Ho could
be a bridge to find Berdugo.
But no,
I don't know where Jin Ho is.
Where could he be?
Did Peter contact Jin Ho?
No, Peter went back
to his province.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WINDOW WHIRRING]
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
[AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING]
Mom...
Mom, hurry...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom, fight, Mom.
I'm Doctor Miguel,
what happened?
She took a lot of medicine.
We don't know how much, Doc.
Her mouth was foaming.
It's a possible drug overdose.
BP, nurse.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Okay, what's happening now
are the effects
of drug overdose that she took.
Most likely, since everything
is slowing down with her...
Did she take painkillers?
Most likely, it's painkillers,
right?
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
Okay, we will do our best.
Okay, we'll do our best.
Please save my mommy.
Do everything for my mom,
- please.
- We will do our best.
We'll do our best.
[SOBBING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Clarissa!
What happened?
Ma'am, I just boiled leaves
for her herbal medicine.
When I went to the room,
she had already collapsed,
and the pills were scattered.
You were with mommy.
Why did you leave her alone?
Hon, you have to calm down.
Why did you neglect her?
What, Clarissa? Answer me!
Hon, you have to calm down.
Clarissa, just go home for now.
We'll take care of this.
We'll call you
when we have news.
Sir, I can wait.
No, we'll handle it.
Ma'am...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS]
It's sad, isn't it?
Because they're leaving one
by one.
I didn't even get
to say goodbye.
That's okay. That's life.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Of course,
we all have our own lives.
We don't need to always be there
for each other, right?
And besides, you didn't even
like them, right?
You just had no choice
because we had a mission.
You're harsh.
I really appreciated what
the four of us built.
What happened to us
wasn't a joke.
We had so many experiences.
And it wasn't easy for you
to understand them.
Because they were like cats
and dogs.
They were always fighting.
Jin Ho and Peter, cat and dog.
When you're around, cat, dog,
and rat.
[CHUCKLES]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You slipped that in.
Rat?
Yes.
Well, it works because...
I'm brainy.
Wow, you even justified it.
Yeah. But my face...
Rat-like.
Very cute, yes.
[SQUEAKS]
Is that right?
[SQUEAKING]
But you know, not a rat, right?
- Cute.
- Okay, then not!
You're defensive.
Affected?
Wow.
Okay, fine, I'm not a rat.
Really?
And we're good now.
What do you mean good?
Wait, why are you angry?
You've been shouting.
And why would I choose
to be angry?
Jin Ho and Peter are gone.
I'm the only one left.
And you're still mad.
But...
[PHONE RINGING]
Wait.
Brainy.
Hello, Yvette?
Andrew...
It's about mommy...
What happened to her?
Just come to the hospital.
Hurry, please.
Okay.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
They said mommy is in
the hospital.
What?
Go see her.
Be careful, okay?
Okay.
You be careful too.
Thanks again.
[SUSPENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Cruz?
Major...
Chief asked me to call to you.
You needed something?
I have something I want you
to find.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom...
Drink this first.
- My child...
- Mom.
Child, this is my fault,
it's my fault.
I told Ma'am Rebecca
I'd only be gone a moment,
but I did so many things.
I even went to the kitchen.
I fixed so many things.
- Mom.
- I should...
I should have said...
I should have checked her first
before doing all that.
It's not your fault.
This is exactly what happened
with your father,
when we thought he was gone.
And I didn't even call him.
I didn't do anything.
Mom, what happened happened.
You didn't fail.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Drink some water first.
What will I do?
I wouldn't be able handle it
if something happens
to Ma'am Rebecca.
I don't know how I'll face
Ma'am Yvette and Sir Andrew,
child.
Mom, breathe first.
One step at a time, Mom.
Think of this for now...
Ma'am Rebecca is already in
the hospital and being treated.
That's what's important, right?
- This is my fault.
- It's not your fault, Mom.
Why did I leave her?
I shouldn't have left her.
Mom...
Drink this first.
[SOBBING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I really checked many times.
No Lee Jin Ho in the database.
Not in police national records.
Even Interpol notice
and Foreign Liaison records,
nothing.
Zero hits, Sir.
That means only two things.
Either his operation is illegal
or off the books.
Black operations?
I don't think so.
Even that has a footprint.
A handler.
An entry clearance.
But here, it's blank.
You know,
that only means one thing.
That's not his real name
and he's not Korean police.
Then who is this Korean?
I don't know.
And why is he here chasing
the syndicate?
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
Yvette, where's mommy?
The medical team is attending
to her.
Where?
Clarissa found her unconscious,
foaming at the mouth,
in her room.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mom...
- Doc...
Sir, Ma'am.
How's my mommy?
Well, she's in critical
condition.
We're still currently trying
to stabilize her.
Her BP's at 64/40,
way below normal.
Her cardiac rate is only at 13,
and she's only breathing
at 50 percent rate.
The amount of drugs
she took earlier
really took a toll on her.
Most likely,
we will need to bring her to
the ICU and also detoxify her.
But as of now, we are still
trying to stabilize her.
That is the current state
we are right now.
Wait, why is mommy overdosed?
Andrew, it's her medication.
And given the quantity,
it looks intentional.
Take that back, Tomas.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Mommy couldn't do that.
- Andrew, stop, please.
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Doc?
- Mom?
Let's start CPR.
Nurse, do an EPI.
Intubate, okay?
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
Mom...
Mom, fight, please.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom...
[FLATLINING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's my fault.
I told Ma'am Rebecca
I'd only be gone a moment,
but I did so many things.
I even went to the kitchen.
I fixed so many things.
Mom, Mom...
I should have checked her
first before doing all that.
It's not your fault.
You just had no choice
because we had a mission then.
I really appreciated
what the four of us built.
What happened to us
wasn't a joke.
Jin Ho and Peter, they're like
cats and dogs.
But when you're around, it would
be a cat, dog, and rat.
It works because I'm brainy.
Rat-like.
Clear!
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
Miss Rebecca was revived.
She's unresponsive.
In short, in layman's terms,
she's in a coma.
We need to put her in the ICU
and detox her.
As to how long she'll be
like this, I cannot say yet.
I'll have the ICU ready.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom...
Can you hear me?
Mom, fight, please, okay?
We will never leave you here.
Mom, fight.
Mom, I can't bear to lose you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's sad, isn't it?
They're leaving one by one.
I didn't even get
to say goodbye.
Of course,
we all have our own lives.
We don't need to always
be there for each other, right?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yvette...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Can we see mom in the ICU later?
Tomas said...
we can look for a bigger
hospital.
Yvette, do you believe
what Tomas said?
Honestly, I don't.
I believe mommy couldn't commit
suicide.
Among us, she was always
the strong one, right?
Even when she was sick.
Like I said,
she often stared blankly,
zoning out.
I don't know if it's the meds
or something else.
So, do you think...
Mommy could really do that?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know.
All of these are just
assumptions,
so I don't know.
[SOBBING]
Yvette stop, please.
You need to go home.
- No, I won't...
- Rest, Yvette.
I won't leave mommy.
I'm not gonna leave her.
I'm not gonna leave mommy.
I'm sure there's nothing
we can do.
Mommy is still in a coma.
Also, maybe the kids are looking
for you.
Yvette...
No, I won't leave mommy.
[SOBBING AND WHIMPERING]
[MIMICS PUNCHES SWOOSHING]
[SIGHS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Still mad I haven't introduced
you to Berdugo?
Does it bother you that you're
still not a part of us?
Listen.
I handled Korean buyers,
and I moved shipments
after port sweep,
but I still haven't met Berdugo.
You're impatient.
No.
I'm underused.
I want to be in the room
where decisions are made.
Trust is layered, Jin Ho.
Trust?
[SCOFFS]
I left my country for you.
Now, I'm burning bridges
for this organization!
Berdugo doesn't show himself
to ambition.
He doesn't just appear,
especially to someone
who's still being...
tested.
You want to meet him?
Prove you can wait.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
You and Lisa will handle
the operation for now.
I know it's heavy,
but I trust you can manage.
Will you be okay there, Boss?
You should have finished
her off.
I should have...
if she wasn't my wife's mother.
But anything more aggressive
would have...
raised questions.
So, nothing that would trigger
an autopsy or a paper trail.
So, you'll make it look
like suicide?
Yes, that way there's
no complications.
Given her condition
and medications,
authorities will read it
as trauma or psychosis.
Tomas?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm so confused who she wanted
to catch.
Who could it be?
Ma'am Yvette? Sir Tomas?
The teddy bear.
Teddy bear?
It had a spy camera.
I'm sure it recorded
what really happened.
Did you notice a teddy bear?
- It was thrown in the trash.
- What?
Be careful, Major. Remember...
The syndicate thinks
you're dead.
Are you sure your informant
hangs out here?
Jin Ho?
Just standby.
Maybe he'll try to escape.
We can chase him.